Finding Aid for the Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, 1967-1993
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Cassettes with Mikhashoff as performer or composer, 1967-1993, I.; Item 1-149
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 135, 13 August 1991 - 15 August 1991, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: August sessions #2 of 4 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Slee Hall, University at Buffalo Dolby B reference copy of DAT master; includes multiple full
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_135_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_135_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_135_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_135_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_135_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_135_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_135_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_135_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_135_02-06sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 136, 13 August 1991 - 15 August 1991, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: August sessions #3 of 4 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Slee Hall, University at Buffalo Dolby B reference copy of DAT master; includes multiple full and partial takes with announcements of works by studio technician Derivative files created: 5 (Box 3, Item 136)
    Contents: Recording session of works, including Griffes: Preludes nos. 1-3; Riegger: Blue voyage; Antheil: #3 (Death of machines?); Hovhaness: Visionary landscapes; Zappa: Piano introduction; Antheil: Valentine waltzes; Ives: Sonata no. 2. Alcotts
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_136_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_136_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_136_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_136_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_136_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_136_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_136_02-03pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_136_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_136_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_136_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_136_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_136_02-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 137, 13 August 1991 - 15 August 1991, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: August sessions #4 of 4 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Slee Hall, University at Buffalo Dolby B reference copy of DAT master; includes multiple full and partial takes with announcements of works by studio technician Derivative files created: 4 (Box 3, Item 137)
    Contents: Recording session of works, including Ruggles: Evocations no.1, no. 2; Rzewski: Piano piece no.4; Ruggles: Evocations no. 3, no. 4
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_137_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_137_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_137_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_137_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_137_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_137_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_137_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_137_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_137_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_137_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 138, 9 November 1991, 1; Container title: November sessions 1 + 2 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Slee Hall, University at Buffalo Cassette missing (Box 3, Item 138)
    Contents: Recording session of works, including Luening: Prelude #4; Gershwin: Impromptu; Bowles: Sonatina F -- Portrait of five; Brant: Music
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 139, 9 November 1991, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: November sessions 3 + 4 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Slee Hall, University at Buffalo Dolby reference copy of DAT master; includes multiple full and partial takes with announcements of works by studio technician Derivative files created: 4 (Box 3, Item 139)
    Contents: Recording session of works, including Brant: Music for a five and dime; Gould: Prelude; Grainger: In a nutshell suite. Pastorale
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_139_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_139_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_139_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_139_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_139_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_139_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_139_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_139_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_139_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_139_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 140, 9 November 1991, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: November sessions 7 + 8 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Slee Hall, University at Buffalo Dolby reference copy of DAT master; includes multiple full and partial takes with announcements of works by studio technician Derivative files created: 6 (Box 3, Item 140)
    Contents: Recording session of works, including Finney: Riddle song; Crawford: Nine preludes. No.6; Vigeland: Nocturne; Glass. Opening; Bernstein: Anniversaries. For Aaron Copland
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_140_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_140_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_140_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_140_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_140_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_140_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_140_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_140_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_140_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_140_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_140_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_140_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_140_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_140_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 141, 9 November 1991, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: November sessions 5 + 6 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Slee Hall, University at Buffalo Dolby reference copy of DAT master; includes multiple full and partial takes with announcements of works by studio technician Derivative files created: 7 (Box 3, Item 141)
    Contents: Recording session of works, including Grainger's In a nutshell suite. Pastorale
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_141_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_141_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_141_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_141_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_141_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_141_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_141_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_141_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_141_02-04pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_141_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_141_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_141_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_141_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_141_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_141_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_141_02-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 142, 10 November 1991, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: November sessions 9 + 10 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Slee Hall, University at Buffalo reference copy of DAT master; includes multiple full and partial takes with announcements of works by studio technician Derivative files created: 11 (Box 3, Item 142)
    Contents: Recording session of works, including Cage: Souvenir; Feldman: Vertical thoughts; Harrison: Waltz; Moran: Waltz
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_142_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_142_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_142_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_142_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_142_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_142_01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_142_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_142_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_142_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_142_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_142_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_142_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_142_02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_142_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_142_02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_142_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_142_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_142_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_142_01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_142_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_142_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_142_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_142_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_142_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_142_02-06sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 143, 10 November 1991, 1 100 minute cassette; Container title: November sessions 11 + 12 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Slee Hall, University at Buffalo Dolby reference copy of DAT master; includes multiple full and partial takes with announcements of works by studio technician Derivative files created: 10 (Box 3, Item 143)
    Contents: Recording session of works, including Thomson: Waltz; Constanten: Dejavalse; Cowell: Amiable conversation; Foss: Solo; Curran: For Cornelius; Tower: Red garnet waltz; Ornstein: Suicide in an airplane
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_143_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_143_02am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_143_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_143_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_143_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_143_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_143_01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_143_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_143_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_143_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_143_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_143_02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 144, 10 November 1991, 1 100 minute cassette; Container title: November sessions 13 + 14 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Slee Hall, University at Buffalo Dolby reference copy of DAT master; includes multiple full and partial takes with announcements of works by studio technician Derivative files created: 8 (Box 3, Item 144)
    Contents: Recording session of works, including Ornstein: Suicide in an airplane; Bernstein: Anniversaries: For Aaron Copland; Hovhaness: Visionary landscapes; Thomson: Portrait 'Bowles' -- Portrait 'Holloway'; Harrison: Sonata; Foss: Solo
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_144_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_144_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_144_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_144_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_144_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_144_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_144_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_144_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_144_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_144_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_144_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_144_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_144_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_144_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_144_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_144_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_144_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_144_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 145, 11 November 1991, 1 100 minute cassette; Container title: November sessions 15 + 16 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Slee Hall, University at Buffalo reference copy of DAT master; includes multiple full and partial takes with announcements of works by studio technician Derivative files created: 3 (Box 3, Item 145)
    Contents: Recording session of works, including Foss: Solo
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_145_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_145_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_145_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_145_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_145_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_145_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_145_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_145_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 146, 11 November 1991, 1 100 minute cassette; Container title: November sessions 17 + 18 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Slee Hall, University at Buffalo Dolby reference copy of DAT master; includes multiple full and partial takes with announcements of works by studio technician Derivative files created: 8 (Box 3, Item 146)
    Contents: Recording session of works, including Thomson: Synthetic waltzes
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_146_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_146_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_146_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_146_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_146_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_146_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_146_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_146_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_146_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_146_02-06pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_146_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_146_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_146_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_146_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_146_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_146_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_146_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_146_02-06sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 147, 11 November 1991, 1 100 minute cassette; Container title: November sessions 19 + 20 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Slee Hall, University at Buffalo reference copy of DAT master; includes multiple full and partial takes with announcements of works by studio technician Derivative files created: 9 (Box 3, Item 147)
    Contents: Recording session of works, including Thomson: Portraits
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_147_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_147_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_147_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_147_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_147_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_147_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_147_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_147_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_147_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_147_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_147_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_147_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_147_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_147_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_147_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_147_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_147_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_147_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_147_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_147_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 148, 8 January 1992, 1 100 minute cassette; Container title: January sessions part 1 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Slee Hall, University at Buffalo Dolby Entitled: Session from my diary III; Annotated: "Tape 1 A"; includes multiple full and partial takes with announcements of works by studio technician Derivative files created: 9 (Box 3, Item 148)
    Contents: Recording session of works, including Harris: Streets of Laredo; Glanville-Hicks: Prelude for a pensive pupil; Bowles: Prelude for GHW; Confrey: Nickel in the slot; Nancarrow: Three 2-part studies for piano
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_148_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_148_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_148_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_148_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_148_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_148_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_148_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_148_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_148_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_148_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_148_02-04pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_148_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_148_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_148_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_148_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_148_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_148_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_148_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_148_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_148_02-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 149, 8 January 1992, 1 100 minute cassette; Container title: January sessions part 2 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Slee Hall, University at Buffalo Dolby Annotated: "Reel 3a"; includes multiple full and partial takes with announcements of works by studio technician Derivative files created: 10 (Box 3, Item 149)
    Contents: Bloch: Chanty; Paulus: Dance; Ince: My friend Mozart; Singleton: Changing faces; Schwantner: Veiled autumn; Copland: The resting place on the hill; Krenek: A boat slowly sailing; Davidovsky: Synchronisms VI
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_149_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_149_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_149_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_149_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_149_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_149_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_149_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_149_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_149_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_149_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_149_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_149_02-04pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_149_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_149_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_149_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_149_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_149_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_149_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_149_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_149_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_149_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_149_02-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 150, 9 January 1992, 1 100 minute cassette; Container title: January sessions part 3 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Slee Hall, University at Buffalo Dolby Annotated: "Tape two A"; includes multiple full and partial takes with announcements of works by studio technician Derivative files created: 1 (Box 3, Item 150)
    Contents: Recording session of works, including Crumb: Makrokosmos
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_150_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_150_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_150_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 151, 11 June 1988, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Montague Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Almeida festival (London, England) Dolby B Derivative files created: 1 (Box 4, Item 151)
    Contents: Montague: Piano concerto
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_151_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_151_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_151_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 152, 11 June 1988, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Montague concerto Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Almeida festival (London, England) Annotated: "Music projects" Check score? Applause after 01-01 and 02-02 Derivative files created: 5 (Box 4, Item 152)
    Contents: Montague: Piano Concerto
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_152_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_152_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_152_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_152_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_152_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_152_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_152_02-03pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_152_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_152_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_152_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_152_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_152_02-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 153, 29 January 1984, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: O. Munoz: Igloo Performers: Mikhashoff, piano and others Recording location: Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Buffalo, N.Y.) Cassette insert contains information about Metropolis: Sydney by Vincent Plush Derivative files created: 2 (Box 4, Item 153)
    Contents: Munoz: Igloo o una naranja
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_153_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_153_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_153_01-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_153_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_153_01-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 154, 28 May 1989, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Music Factory Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Bergen (Norway) Check Derivative files created: 6 (Box 4, Item 154)
    Contents: Ives; Nancarrow; Cage: Furniture music -- Cinema
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_154_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_154_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_154_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_154_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_154_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_154_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_154_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_154_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_154_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_154_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_154_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_154_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_154_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_154_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 155, 15 June 1988, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Music for 4 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Arditti String Quartet; Nigel Hinds, gentleman Recording location: Almeida festival (London, England) Dolby C Program entitled: Music for 4, more or less Check Derivative files created: 4 (Box 4, Item 155)
    Contents: Zimmermann: Presence
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_155_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_155_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_155_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_155_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_155_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_155_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_155_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_155_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_155_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_155_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 156, 29 June 1976, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Music when soft voices die Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location OK Derivative files created: 5 (Box 4, Item 156)
    Contents: Newell: Sonnet; Rothstein: Lines; Smit: A mountain eulogy; Radecke: Flashing silver nails; Vigeland: Ardor
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_156_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_156_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_156_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_156_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_156_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_156_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_156_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_156_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_156_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_156_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_156_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_156_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 157, 6 July 1982, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: NMA 7-6-82 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: New Music America festival (Chicago, Ill.) Contents from printed program 6 works, 7 files Derivative files created: 7 (Box 4, Item 157)
    Contents: Becker: Soundpiece no.5; J. Sellars: Sonata no.2; Curran: For Cornelius; Foss: Solo; Rudhyar: Rite of transcendance; Rzewski: Piano piece no.4
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_157_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_157_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_157_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_157_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_157_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_157_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_157_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_157_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_157_02-03pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_157_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_157_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_157_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_157_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_157_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_157_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_157_02-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 158, 20 April 1989, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: NANMF / BPO 89 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra Recording location: North American New Music Festival (Buffalo, N.Y.) Derivative files created: 5 (Box 4, Item 158)
    Contents: Messiaen: Les offrandes oubliées; Druckman: Viola concerto; Xenakis: Syrmos
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_158_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_158_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_158_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_158_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_158_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_158_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_158_02-03pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_158_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_158_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_158_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_158_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_158_02-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 159, 30 April 1981, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: NUMUS Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Katedralskolens Festsal, Aarhus, Denmark Dolby B Derivative files created: 3 (Box 4, Item 159)
    Contents: Wolff: Preludes for piano; Norholm: Discourse on time; Rzewski: Four pieces: IV
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_159_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_159_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_159_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_159_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_159_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_159_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_159_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_159_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 160, 19 April 1986, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Nancarrow at Lincoln center Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Lincoln center, NY and Holland festival Studies arranged by Yvar Mikhashoff Derivative files created: 9 (Box 4, Item 160)
    Contents: Nancarrow: Study no. 6 -- Study no. 3 -- ?Tango? -- Study no. 15 -- Study no. 16 -- Study no. 6 -- Studies nos. 15, 14, 5, 6, 14
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_160_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_160_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_160_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_160_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_160_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_160_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_160_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_160_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_160_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_160_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_160_02-05pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_160_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_160_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_160_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_160_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_160_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_160_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_160_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_160_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_160_02-05sc.mp3